Kirito...
Did you carry me all the way up here?
Damn right I did.
And it wasn't easy.
Maybe a thank you, or a...
What are you doing?
How disgusting!
You're completely drenched in sweat!
And you have stained my garments!
How dare you follow them up!
Are you kidding?
and I've opened my eyes I've made my eyes,
and I've made my path to you
I'm proud of myself Help! Help!
Where is your partner?
Hey, his name's Eugeo.
Fine, Eugeo.
He is not here.
From the cloud-top garden,
there is a stairway leading up.
Before reaching this floor, however, he
would have had to face our strongest knight.
Yeah, and who would that be?
Uncle.
Or rather, Commander Bercouli.
Oh man, now what?
I know.
System call.
Generate Umbra Element.
Adhere Possession.
Object ID, WLSS-703.
Discharge.
What are you doing that for?
I'm trying to find where
the Blue Rose Sword's at.
If I can find it, I'm gonna find him.
He's under us.
One moment.
You did this, I take it? Yeah.
I managed to stop the bleeding, but
my sacred arts can only do so much.
Do you think you can
heal your eye yourself?
Not now.
There is not enough
sacred power in the air.
I cannot repair it until Solus has risen.
I am still feeling some pain, and
depth perception will be an issue.
But neither will keep me from fighting.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I wish to feel this pain.
It is the proof of my
resolve to fight the church.
I am fine.
Okay.
I get it.
And if we're ever in battle, I'll
make sure to protect your right.
Is Yujiho the one responsible for this?
I'm pretty sure it was him.
I mean, remember how he activated
perfect control on us before?
To be honest, I didn't
think it was this powerful.
It can't be. Uncle!
What the?
Uncle!
No way.
Eugeo didn't do that to him.
He did not, but I have an idea who did.
Years ago,
Uncle told me that Prime
Senator Chudelkin had
been granted the authority
to turn anyone to stone.
An art called Deep Freeze.
Really?
But they're supposed
to be on the same side.
Why would he betray
one of his own knights?
Doesn't make sense.
I think Uncle secretly harbored doubts
about the orders issued by the Senate.
And yet,
like myself,
he believed there could be no peace in
the realm without the rule of the Church.
So he continued to perform
his duties regardless.
The senator may have all
the authority, but this…
There is no reason to
treat him so horribly!
Son! Uncle!
Uncle!
No, you mustn't try to move!
You'll destroy yourself! Stop it!
Hey, little girl.
Why don't you cut out that crying?
A smile suits you better.
Uncle!
Look at you.
I guess you made it over that wall, kiddo.
For 300 years, I tried.
Couldn't break the seal. But you did.
What do I do?
I can't just leave you here.
Don't you fuss over me.
I'm happy for you.
You're stronger than ever.
There's nothing left for me to teach you.
What are you saying?
That is not true.
There is so much I need to learn from you.
You know all you need.
If anyone can guide this world to
where it ought to be, it's you.
Hey, punk.
Look after her for me.
You got it.
You want to find your partner,
Prime Senator Judelkin?
He took him.
Heading to the Pontifex's chamber.
However, hurry before the kid gets
trapped in the maze of his memories.
Thank you, Uncle.
No way.
some have tried to wield two
swords before mostly pretentious
upper-class noblemen looking to
impress you oddly enough seem
rather imposing oh you think I
can't imagine fighting with two
swords though that'd be crazy
all right by all accounts we must
assume the pontifex has eugeo by
now when she speaks one cannot
resist her words are a web which
entangle the mind like some kind
of hypnotist you talked to her
before only once it was six years
ago i remember waking up and
the Pontifex standing before me.
She said she ruled the human empire
on behalf of the gods and had
summoned me to serve their will.
Her eyes were like mirrors,
silver, and reflective.
I did not realize it at
the time, but I do now.
I was terrified of her, and
I knew I could not defy her.
I would accept every word she said
and serve her with all of my being.
The fear was absolute.
It compelled me to obey,
and like a coward, I did.
Alice.
Not to worry.
I know what I must do now.
For the sake of my sister
living in the North,
for my family and the citizens of this
realm, I will do what I believe is right.
We must hurry.
Time is short, and we still
have to reach the Pontifex.
The Prime Senator will try to
stop us, so prepare yourself.
Wait, what about the commander?
We can't leave him like this.
If we catch Chudelkin, we can
force him to reverse the spell.
Or we can kill him and
solve the problem that way.
Hey. Yes?
You mentioned this Prime Senator
Chudelkin guy a few times.
But what's the deal
with the other senators?
To be honest, none of us Integrity
Knights have ever seen the other Senators.
I know they are located
above the 96th floor.
We Knights are not allowed there, though.
You know what these Senators do?
They monitor the realm.
From their chamber,
they observe the words
and deeds of every citizen
to ensure they are not
violating the Taboo Index.
When someone runs afoul of the taboos,
they note the violation and
send a knight to deal with it.
So basically, they're pretty much
the eyes and ears of the Pontifex.
Although,
if Administrator's a control freak,
it's hard to believe she'd give
anyone that much authority.
Is this where they are?
Yes, it should be.
That is a sacred art.
Doesn't sound like an attack spell.
Are you ready?
They're all just heads. Look again.
Their bodies seem to be attached.
that was a senator have
you seen one before
yeah back at the academy
right after we fought
But Rios and Humber, he
appeared out of nowhere.
These miserable creatures
are the Senators?
What a horrifying fate.
Did the Pontifex do this?
Yeah, that's my bet.
These were once normal people.
Probably good at the sacred arts, too.
She kidnapped them and turned
them into these things.
Unforgivable.
No!
This will not - Who's that?
The Prime Senator...
Judelkin.
This cannot be happening!
This won't do! No, no, no!
It simply will not do!
Oh!
If you attempt to initiate an art, I will
cut your tongue right out of your head.
That nerve!
Wait just a moment.
You should have died in
the fall with that traitor.
Why are you alive, Number 30?
I am not a number.
My name is Alice.
I am no longer number 30.
You!
Why are you here? Number...
I mean Alice.
Why is your sword not embedded in him?
Don't you remember?
He's a heretic, a traitor, a pawn
of the Dark Territory! You're right.
He is a traitor.
But he is not from the Dark Territory.
That I can assure you.
You miserable knight!
You wish to betray us too!
When I tell you to do
something, you damn well do it!
You are nothing but a puppet!
All you knights are!
The Axiom Church turned us into puppets.
You sealed away our memories
through the Synthesis ritual,
forced us to be loyal
to you and the Church,
made us believe the myth that we were
knights summoned from the heavens.
Yes, you are correct.
I remember the day we turned
you like it was yesterday.
You were so young, so innocent, so cute,
begging as tears streamed down your cheeks.
Please, don't take away my
memories of all the people I love!
Don't make me forget!
Why,
just thinking about it again is going to
keep me awake all night
laughing hysterically.
As I recall,
you were brought here
from some backwater town
and trained as an
apprentice for two years.
You were so rebellious!
Once you snuck out to see the
Midsummer Festival like a tomboy.
That said,
you studied hard, believing against all
hope that one day you'd return home again?
But you didn't.
And that's because,
once you've raised your system
control authority level high enough?
It's forced synthesis time!
You should have seen your face when you
realized you'd never see your home again.
I wanted to turn you to
stone so I could display
your precious grief in my chamber forever.
You mentioned something odd just now.
Forced synthesis?
Do you mean to say the ritual can
be undertaken voluntarily as well?
My, my, what sharp ears you have.
You're absolutely correct.
Six years ago, you were
so unbelievably stubborn,
you refused to recite the secret commands
for the typical synthesis ritual.
Honestly, you were the most
insufferable brat imaginable.
You gave me no choice but to divert the
automated senators from their normal duties,
then have them conduct a ritual to pry the
door open to your most precious memories.
It was a bother, but I shouldn't complain.
I got to see an incredible show!
He's talking way too much.
Yeah.
Like he's stalling.
Prime Senator Chudelkin,
you had a lifetime of
amusement from my suffering.
Now, at the end, I hope you are satisfied.
I have had enough of your dribble.
And you.
You fools!
The ritual is not all I'm good at!
I will kill him.
Hey, wait up!
System call!
Generate humanist enemy!
Be on guard for a surprise attack.
You got it.
He was chanting from here a moment ago.
The hundredth floor is above
us, so perhaps he fled there.
But how?
I don't see stairs anywhere. Do you?
Great, another Integrity Knight.
No, that can't be.
Yu-Gi-Oh!
What the hell?
But how?
It's too soon!
Too soon for what?
The synthesis ritual.
Your friend Yu-Gi-Oh seems to
have already been synthesized.
He is?
No way. You sure? I am.
I do not know how it is possible.
He fought the commander only an hour ago.
Then it's not possible.
Wait. Not him.
What are you doing?
Do not lose your wits now.
There is still a chance we can
save you, Geo. There is? Yes.
You told me so yourself.
You discovered a way to restore
an Integrity Knight's memories.
Therefore, it should apply to him as well.
The important thing now is you stay
calm and get hold of yourself. Yeah.
Let me handle this.
As you wish.
Be careful.
He is not the person you once knew. Right.
Eugeo, you remember who I am?
I'm Kirito.
I'm your best friend.
We've been together ever since
we left Rulid two years ago.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who you are.
Thank you, though.
For what?
For returning my sword to me.
Incarnate arms.
How'd he do that?
He used an ancient art
taught to Integrity Knights.
It is neither sacred
art nor perfect control.
It allows one to move objects at will.
Only a handful of knights, including
Uncle, have the skill to use it, though.
It is not something a newly created
knight like Eugeo could have mastered.
You got it back.
So now what?
I will fight the both of you.
It is what my lady wishes.
Oh, come on.
You're going to fight me, your friend?
All because she told you to?
That's no reason to fight.
It is reason enough for me.
She gives me everything I ever wanted.
And she is all I'll ever need now.
Give me a break.
What about Alice?
Do you remember her?
I don't.
And I don't want to.
I don't care who either of you are.
I've had enough.
Snap out of it.
Arm yourself.
I am done talking.
You don't remember,
but I'm the one who taught
you how to fight with a sword.
Keep that in mind, cause I'm
about to teach you another lesson.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh,
oh,
oh, oh
Don't love me, I want you to protect
me, and I want you to give a hand.
I won't be facing my hand, I can't do it.
But I can't say anything, life goes on.
Everything turns to ash to ash.
My life will be my path.
With the pain and pain,
And everything turns to
dust to dust When you die
and die in the water If
there's only a small flower,
Forgive me no more.
The thirty-second night.